Guide to the Records of Amnesty International of the USA, Inc.
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Membership Mobilization, 1971-1995
  - Subseries IV.2: Local and Student Groups, 1971-1994.
    - Sub-subseries IV.2.2: Local Groups, 1971-1994
      - Group Files--Closed Groups
        - USA #20--Oberlin, Ohio
          - 1972-1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
          - 1972-1983 [restricted until 2052] (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - USA #32--Eugene, Oregon
          - 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 24)
          - 1975-1981 [restricted until 2055] (Box 28, Folder 25)
        - USA #36--Cambridge, Massachusetts
          - 1975-1986 (Box 28, Folder 26)
          - 1975-1986 [restricted until 2056] (Box 28, Folder 27)
        - USA #41--Placentia, California (Box 29)
          - 1973-1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - 1973-1980 [restricted until 2051] (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - USA #41--Jacksonville, Florida, 1980-1981 [restricted until 2057] (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - USA #42--Long Beach, California
          - 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
          - 1973-1978 [restricted until 2051] (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - USA #44--San Francisco, California
          - 1974-1979 (Box 29, Folder 6)
          - 1974-1979 [restricted until 2055] (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - USA #46--Fort Worth, Texas, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - USA #47--Bellingham, Washington, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - USA #51--Kingston, Pennsylvania
          - 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
          - 1977-1980 [restricted until 2055] (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - USA #51--Jackson, Mississippi
          - 1980-1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
          - 1980-1982 [restricted until 2056] (Box 29, Folder 13)
        - USA #52--La Jolla, California, 1975-1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - USA #52--La Jolla, California, 1975-1979 [restricted until 2051] (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - USA #53--Camden, New Jersey, 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - USA #55--San Rafael, California, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - USA #59--Binghamton, New York
          - 1977-1988 (Box 29, Folder 18)
          - 1977-1988 [restricted until 2058] (Box 29, Folder 19)
        - USA #63--Coalinga, California
          - 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 20)
          - 1973-1978 [restricted until 2053] (Box 29, Folder 21)
        - USA #68--Memphis, Tennessee
          - 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 22)
          - 1977-1978 [restricted until 2054] (Box 29, Folder 23)
        - USA #69--Cambridge, Massachusetts
          - 1975-1986 (Box 29, Folder 24)
          - 1975-1986 [restricted until 2060] (Box 29, Folder 25)
        - USA #72--Little Rock, Arkansas
          - 1977-1983 (Box 29, Folder 26)
          - 1977-1983 [restricted until 2056] (Box 29, Folder 27)
        - USA #77--Fort Wayne, Indiana
          - 1974-1981 (Box 29, Folder 28)
          - 1974-1981 [restricted until 2055] (Box 29, Folder 29)
        - USA #89--Salt Lake City, Utah, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 30)
        - USA #91--Fort Collins, Colorado
          - 1977-1981 (Box 29, Folder 31)
          - 1977-1981 [restricted until 2057] (Box 29, Folder 32)
        - USA #99--Storrs, Connecticut
          - 1975-1982 (Box 29, Folder 33)
          - 1975-1982 [restricted until 2055] (Box 29, Folder 34)
        - USA #102--Erie, Pennsylvania, 1975-1979 (Box 29, Folder 35)
        - USA #103--Honolulu, Hawaii
          - 1977-1987 (Box 29, Folder 36)
          - 1977-1987 [restricted until 2063] (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - USA #108--Sacramento, California
          - 1977-1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
          - 1977-1984 [restricted until 2057] (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - USA #114--Vermillion, South Dakota, 1977-1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - USA #117--Capitol Area, New York (Albany, Schenectady, Troy)
          - 1978-1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
          - 1978-1987 [restricted until 2054] (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - USA #119--Springfield, Vermont
          - 1978-1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
          - 1978-1986 [restricted until 2057] (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - USA #120--Waco, Texas, 1977-1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - USA #121--Colorado Springs, Colorado
          - 1977-1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
          - 1977-1982 [restricted until 2058] (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - USA #123--Grand Rapids, Michigan
          - 1978-1984 (Box 30, Folder 12)
          - 1978-1984 [restricted until 2058] (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - USA #124--Champaign-Urbana, Illinois, 1975-1979 (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - USA #127--College Station, Texas, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - USA #130--Riverdale, New York City, New York (Bronx)
          - 1978-1987 (Box 30, Folder 16)
          - 1978-1987 [restricted until 2055] (Box 30, Folder 17)
        - USA #131--Miami, Florida
          - 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 18)
          - 1978-1981 [restricted until 2056] (Box 30, Folder 19)
        - USA #132--St. Petersburg, Florida
          - 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 20)
          - 1978-1981 [restricted until 2055] (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - USA #140--Lehigh Valley, Pennsylvania
          (Allentown, Bethlehem)
          - 1978-1982 (Box 30, Folder 22)
          - 1978-1982 [restricted until 2058] (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - USA #141--Springfield, Massachusetts
          - 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
          - 1978-1980 [restricted until 2054] (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - USA #150--Los Angeles, California--Los Angeles Lawyers' Committee
          - 1978-1982 (Box 30, Folder 26)
          - 1978-1982 [restricted until 2057] (Box 30, Folder 27)
        - USA #154--Harrison, New York (Mid-Westchester County)
          - 1979-1987 (Box 30, Folder 28)
          - 1979-1987 [restricted until 2060] (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - USA #155--Duxbury, Massachusetts
          (Plymouth County)
          - 1979-1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
          - 1979-1987 [restricted until 2061] (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - USA #160--Morgantown, West Virginia
          - 1978-1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
          - 1978-1985 [restricted until 2055] (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - USA #164--Holland, Michigan
          - 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
          - 1979-1982 [restricted until 2056] (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - USA #170--Winston-Salem, North Carolina
          - 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
          - 1979-1982 [restricted until 2054] (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - USA #171--Greensboro, North Carolina
          - 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
          - 1979-1982 [restricted until 2057] (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - USA #179--Indianapolis, Indiana
          - 1979-1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
          - 1979-1982 [restricted until 2057] (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - USA #180--Boston, Massachusetts
          - 1979-1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
          - 1979-1985 [restricted until 2057] (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - USA #183--Salt Lake City, Utah
          - 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 16)
          - 1979-1981 [restricted until 2057] (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - USA #185--Salem, Oregon
          - 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 18)
          - 1979-1983 [restricted until 2057] (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - USA #199--Pensacola, Florida
          - 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
          - 1980-1981 [restricted until 2056] (Box 31, Folder 21)
        - USA #201--Kingston, Rhode Island
          - 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 22)
          - 1980-1986 [restricted until 2060] (Box 31, Folder 23)
        - USA #203--Sanford, Maine
          - 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 24)
          - 1980-1984 [restricted until 2059] (Box 31, Folder 25)
        - USA #210--South Royalton, Vermont
          - 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 26)
          - 1980-1983 [restricted until 2058] (Box 31, Folder 27)
        - USA #216--Columbus, Indiana (Box 32)
          - 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
          - 1981-1982 [restricted until 2058] (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - USA #220--Port Angeles, Washington
          - 1981-1984 (Box 32, Folder 3)
          - 1981-1984 [restricted until 2058] (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - USA #221--Beaumont, Texas
          - 1981-1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
          - 1981-1987 [restricted until 2057] (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - USA #222--Tacoma, Washington
          - 1981-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
          - 1981-1984 [restricted until 2057] (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - USA #225--El Prado, New Mexico
          - 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 9)
          - 1981-1983 [restricted until 2057] (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - USA #227--Kennebec Valley, Maine (Hallowell), 1981-1985 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - USA #231--San Francisco, California, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - USA #232--Salina, Kansas
          - 1981-1987 (Box 32, Folder 13)
          - 1981-1987 [restricted until 2063] (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - USA #236--West Palm Beach, Florida, 1981-1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - USA #241--Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts, 1981-1987 (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - USA #243--Missoula, Montana, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - USA #245--Eugene, Oregon, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - USA #246--Miami, Florida, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - USA #247--Columbia, Missouri, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - USA #249--Fort Lauderdale, Florida, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - USA #251--John Jay College of Criminal Justice, New York City, New York, 1982-1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
        - USA #257--Jackson Heights, New York City, New York, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - USA #260--New York City, New York (Manhattan), 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - USA #261--Dallas, Texas, 1982-1987 (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - USA #265--New York City, New York (Manhattan), 1982-1985 (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - USA #268--Rockford, Illinois, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 27)
        - USA #276--Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 28)
        - USA #279--Williamstown, Massachusetts
          - 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 29)
          - 1983-1986 [restricted until 2060] (Box 32, Folder 30)
        - USA #285--Pancho Bernando, California, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 31)
        - USA #287--Peru, Illinois, 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
        - USA #290--Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - USA #291--Ashland/Medford, Oregon, 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 34)
        - USA #293--Torrington, Connecticut, 1983-1987 (Box 32, Folder 35)
        - USA #303--Cordova, Alaska
          - 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 36)
          - 1984-1986 [restricted until 2060] (Box 32, Folder 37)
        - USA #351--Pelham, New York
          - 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 38)
          - 1987-1988 [restricted until 2063] (Box 32, Folder 39)
        - USA #400--Cocoa, Florida, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 40)
        - USA #401--McAllen, Texas, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 41)
        - USA #405--Corpus Christi, Texas
          - 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 42)
          - 1985-1986 [restricted until 2061] (Box 32, Folder 43)
        - USA #406--Wilmington, North Carolina, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Sub-subseries IV.2.3: Student Groups, 1977-1993
      This subseries consists of files on campus and high school groups. The files include sign-up forms, assessment returns, annual reports and questionnaires. The files also include subject files on the New York City High School Cluster and the coordination of high school groups.
      - Campus and High School Groups (Box 1)
        - Assessment Returns, 1989-1990, (4 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
        - Assessments, circa 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
          (Log Book)
        - Correspondence--A-Y, 1982-1984, (4 Folders) (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
        - Sign-Up Forms
          - College Groups (Box 2)
            - 1987 Fall, (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
            - 1991 Spring (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - High School Groups
            - 1987 Fall, (3 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
            - 1991 Spring (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Campus Network
        - Action Sheets, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - Annual Reports, 1986-1987, (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
        - Closed Groups (Reports), 1984 February-1984 May (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Comparison Figures by Region and Lists of Groups by State, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence on, 1977-1982, (3 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
        - Handbooks, circa 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - List of Groups, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Past Programs, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Questionnaire (Original), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Questionnaires from Active Groups, 1981, (3 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 2-4)
        - Questionnaires from Closed Groups, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - High School Coordinator
        - General, 1990-1991, (2 Folders) (Folder 6-7)
          - Addresses
            - Old Cluster Addresses
              - 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
              - 1989-1993 [restricted until 2069] (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - AI Info [Material for Groups], circa 1980s-1990, (4 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
        - Children Pamphlets, circa 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - Children for Children's Human Rights
          - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
            (Includes "The Colors of Hope" packet)
          - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
          - Curriculum, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
          - Diskettes, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
            (5" Diskettes)
          - Seminars I and II, 1989 April-1989 May (Box 5, Folder 10)
          - United Nations Documents on Health Care and AIDS, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
          - United Nations Children's Fund (UNICEF) Packet, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Death Penalty
          - Comprehensive Violent Crime Control Act of 1991, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
          - Our Disappeared, 1990 October (Box 5, Folder 14)
          - Powell Commission report on Federal Habeas Corpus in Capital Cases, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
          - Unfiled/Loose, circa 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - Israel--Children as Targets: A Report on Military Violence Against Children in the Occupied Territories (Appendix), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Northeast Regional Conference, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - Planning Notes, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - South Africa--Silencing Dissent in South Africa (Handout), circa 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Students for Students
          - Campaign, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
          - Peru Information Package, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - Unfinished Business
          - circa 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
          - circa 1989-1991 [restricted until 2067] (Box 6, Folder 10)
        - United States--U.S. HUMAN RIGHTS POLICY: AN AIUSA POSITION PAPER, 1984 May (Box 6, Folder 11)
        - What is a Cluster?, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - New York City High School Cluster
        - Actions, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
        - AIUSA Group Media Workbook, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        - Big Picture Workshop, 1988 December 16 (Box 6, Folder 15)
        - "The Break in the Chain" [Newsletter], circa 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
        - Campus Group Work, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        - Children's Edition Urgent Action Packet, circa 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        - Children for Children's Human Rights, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
        - Education Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        - Events, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        - Handouts, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
        - Information Sheet, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
        - Jamnesty (Box 7)
          - Nina's Jamnesty '88 Stuff, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
          - Notes and Planning, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
          - Jamnesty '89
            - 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
            - Contracts, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        - McBride, Robert (South Africa), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        - Mandate Workshops, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - Minutes / Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous / History, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        - New York City Area High School Groups Conference, 1987 November 21 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        - Northeast Regional Conference, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        - Old Cases and Articles, circa 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
        - Orientation Committee, circa 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
        - Orientation Packet, circa 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
        - Packet, circa 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
        - Planning Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Position Papers, circa 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Public Speaking, 1984-1987, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Public Speaking, Ideas for, circa 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Publicity, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
        - Recruitment, 1988-1991 [restricted until 2067] (Box 8, Folder 7)
        - Steering Committee, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
        - Telephone Tree, 1988 [restricted until 2063] (Box 8, Folder 9)
        - Universal Declaration of Human Rights--40th Anniversary, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Series V: Country Coordination Groups (Co-Groups), 1978-1995
  Country Coordination Groups (co-groups) are volunteer groups that have expertise on a particular country or region. This program is also known as the Country Specialist Program. These groups help to manage the country-related work of AIUSA and act as liaisons on casework issues among local groups, sections and the International Secretariat.
  - Subseries V.1: General, 1978-1988
    These files are the records of Pat Bronstein Kos and Sheila Dauer. The records include general information on the purpose and functionality of country coordination groups, as well as correspondence and materials related to activities, budgets, country work, formation, monthly mailings, planning and priorities, policy discussions, structure, and training.
    - Co-Group Members List, 1989 July and circa 1990 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Compendium for Coordination Groups/Coordinators (ORG 43/03/86), 1986 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Co-Groups--By Region, 1978-1980
      (Unless Otherwise Noted)
      - Central America Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - China Co-Group, 1989 (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - Eastern Europe Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - Ethiopia Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 6)
      - Indonesia Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Middle East Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - Philippines Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - Rhodesia Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 10)
        (Zimbabwe)
      - South Africa Co-Group / Namibia Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 11)
      - South America Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 12)
      - South Korean Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 13)
      - Taiwan Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 14)
      - Uganda Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 15)
      - Uruguay Co-Group (Box 264, Folder 16)
      - USSR Co-Group
        (Soviet Coordination Group)
        - General (Box 264, Folder 17)
        - Madness: A Documentary (Box 264, Folder 18)
          (Play by Beth Goldring)
        - Newsletters, 1980-1985 (Box 264, Folder 19)
    - Co-Groups--General
      - Budgets for Co-Groups, FY 1981 (Box 264, Folder 20)
      - Casework Standards, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 264, Folder 22)
      - Country Planning and Priorities
        - 1984 (Box 264, Folder 23)
        - 1985 (Box 264, Folder 24)
        - 1988 (Box 264, Folder 25)
          (Includes Annual Review of Country Work papers)
      - General, 1978-1980, (3 Folders) (Box 265, Folder 1, 1a, 2)
      - Impartiality Issue, 1983 (Box 265, Folder 3)
        (Includes Co-Group discussion on, and Task Force on Impartiality Report, 1982 June)
      - International Secretariat (IS)--Documents Re: Co-Groups, 1979 (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Materials to be Given to Prospects, circa 1978 (Box 265, Folder 5)
        (Includes general information on Co-Groups, and meeting materials of Co-Group Meeting of 1978 September 13)
      - Meeting
        - 1979 February 7 (Box 265, Folder 6)
        - 1980 February 29-March 2 (Box 265, Folder 7)
      - Monthly Mailings to Co-Groups
        - 1982, (2 Folders) (Box 265, Folder 8-9)
        - 1983 (Box 265, Folder 10)
          (#3, 7, 9-12)
        - 1984 (Box 265, Folder 11)
          (#1-6, 8-11)
        - 1985 (Box 265, Folder 12)
          (#1-5, 7-12)
        - 1986, (2 Folders) (Box 265, Folder 13-14)
      - Policy Issues/Disc., 1986 (Box 266, Folder 1)
        (Various issues including impartiality and country planning and priorities)
      - Prospective, 1978-1979 (Box 266, Folder 2)
        (Includes information on prospective co-group formation and coordinators)
      - Reports
        - Quarterly, 1978 (Box 266, Folder 3)
        - Semi-Annual, 1979 June (Box 266, Folder 4)
      - What Coordination Groups Do, 1982 March (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Subseries V.2: Sheila Dauer Files, 1988-1995
    Dauer's files include training materials for country coordination groups and files related to their activities, campaigns, country work, policy issues, and other general subjects.
    - AI Week 1995 The Front Line-Human Rights Defenders at Risk, 1995 (Box ###, Folder 6)
    - Advertising--Ad Policy Guidelines and Procedures, 1988 May 24 (Box ###, Folder 7)
    - Africa--Co-Group Meeting and Action, 1989 December 2 (Box ###, Folder 8)
      (Includes case histories)
    - Campaign Training Module, 1990 August (Box ###, Folder 9)
    - Campaigns, 1992-1995 (Box ###, Folder 10)
      (Corporate approaches, includes letters)
    - Co-Group Member Training
      (Packets)
      - 1989-1991 (Box ###, Folder 11)
      - 1993 February 20-21 (Box ###, Folder 12)
      - 1994 February 19-20 (Box ###, Folder 13)
    - Crisis Response/Rapid Action Station, 1993-1995 (Box ###, Folder 14)
      (Files contains information on a number countries, correspondence, etc.)
    - Do Not Fear the Storm, circa 1984-1985 (Box ###, Folder 15)
      (Prisoner stories, letter to AI, includes photos)
    - Eliminations and Terror--International Conference on Political Killings and Disappearances (Amsterdam), 1992 September 4-6 (Box ###, Folder 16-17)
      (Includes lists of participants, agenda, briefs of papers, and the papers themselves)
    - Finance Guidelines for Local Groups and Clusters, 1994-1996 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - General, 1986 (Box 267, Folder 2)
      (Includes materials related to country work planning and reviews, including Annual Review of Country Work (ARCW), planning, IEC Report, etc.)
    - Impunity Teach-Ins, 1994-1995 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - International Secretariat (IS)--Implementation of the Decisions of the 1987 International Council Meeting (ICM) and IS Priorities for 1988/1989, 1988 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - National Campaign Department--Budgets, FY 1989-1990, 1992, 1993 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - National Student Program--Action Booklet, 1994-1995 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Scholastic Inc. New York City--Human Rights Education Campaign, 1993 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Speaker's List (AI), 1995 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Summit of the Americas (Miami), 1994 December 9-11, (4 Folders) (Box 267, Folder 9-12)
      (AIUSA activities during)
    - United Nations (UN) World Conference on Human Rights (Vienna), 1993 June 14-25 (Box 267, Folder 13-16)
    - Urgent Actions, 1988 May (Box 267, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Networks, 1975-1995
  Networks serve to organize individuals who have chosen to use their professional training for human rights work.
  - Subseries VI.1: Educators Network, 1987-1990
    The Educator’s Network of AIUSA serves to facilitate and promote the development and exchange among educators of effective strategies for teaching about human rights. This series consists of three files of correspondence and registration sheets.
    - 1987-1990, (3 Folders) (Box 268, Folder 1-3)
      (Mostly registration sheets)
  - Subseries VI.2: Health Professionals Network (HPN), 1974-1989